seoinc.com 2019-12-06

# SEO Inc. Legal and Privacy Policy Updated Septermer 2019

## SEO Inc: Web Site Privacy Policy compliant with GDPR (EU Privacy law)

 **Effective date: May 24, 2019**  
Search Engine Optimization Inc (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the [https://www.seoinc.com](https://www.seoinc.com/)  website (the “Service”).  
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from [https://www.seoinc.com ](https://www.seoinc.com/)

 **Service**  
Service is the [https://www.seoinc.com](https://www.seoinc.com/)  website operated by Search Engine Optimization Inc​​​  
**Personal Data**  
Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).​  
**Usage Data**  
Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).​  
**Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).​  
**Data Controller**  
Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.​  
**Data Processors (or Service Providers)**  
Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.  
We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.​  
**Data Subject (or User)**  
Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.

### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

•    Email address  
•    First name and last name  
•    Phone number  
•    Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City  
•    Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

### Tracking Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information. Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

 **Examples of Cookies we use:**

•     **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.  
•     **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.  
•     **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

 **Search Engine Optimization Inc uses the collected data for various purposes:**

•    To provide and maintain our Service  
•    To notify you about changes to our Service  
•    To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so  
•    To provide customer support  
•    To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service  
•    To monitor the usage of our Service  
•    To detect, prevent and address technical issues  
•    To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information.

## Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Search Engine Optimization Inc legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Search Engine Optimization Inc may process your Personal Data because:

 **•     We need to perform a contract with you**  
 **•     You have given us permission to do so**  
 **•     The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights**  
 **•     To comply with the law**

Search Engine Optimization Inc will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Search Engine Optimization Inc will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Search Engine Optimization Inc will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

###  **Business Transaction**

If Search Engine Optimization Inc is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

###  **Disclosure for Law Enforcement**

Under certain circumstances, Search Engine Optimization Inc may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

###  **Legal Requirements**

Search Engine Optimization Inc may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

•    To comply with a legal obligation  
•    To protect and defend the rights or property of Search Engine Optimization Inc  
•    To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service  
•    To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public  
•    To protect against legal liability

### Security of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### “Do Not Track” Signals

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Search Engine Optimization Inc aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

 **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.** Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.  
 **The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.  
 **The right to object.** You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.  
 **The right of restriction.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.  
 **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.  
 **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Search Engine Optimization Inc relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

###  **Analytics**

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

###  **Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

### **Behavioral Remarketing**

Search Engine Optimization Inc uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

###  **Google AdWords**

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads/](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

###  **Facebook**

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: [https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950/](https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950)

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217/](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada [http://youradchoices.ca/ ](https://youradchoices.ca/)or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation/](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children’s Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.  
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## SEO Inc. Legal and Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Search Engine Optimization Inc. or SEO Inc. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

•    What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.  
•    What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.  
•    The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.  
•    How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third parties outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

### Tags

We also use “web beacons,” “pixel tags,” “clear GIFs,” or similar means (individually or collectively “Tags”) on our Website. A Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel, embedded on web pages. Tags are ordinarily not visible to users. Tags allow us to count the number of users who have visited certain pages of the Website, to deliver branded services, and to generate statistics about how our Website is used.

We use the services of third party companies to help us carry out and measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns. For example, these third party companies may ensure that you are shown ads at appropriate frequencies, so that you do not see the same ad repeatedly. As part of these services, one or more Tags may be placed on the Website. These Tags do not enable third parties to collect your name, e-mail address, phone number, or other similar information that directly identifies you. Rather, when you visit the Website, these Tags will direct your web browser to contact these third party companies, at which time they may set or read a cookie on your device and collect information about your visit – such as your IP address, cookie ID, which parts of the websites are viewed or clicked, and date/time information.

Currently, we use our own Tags on the Website to enable collection of information about visitors to our Website.

We use information collected from Tags to gather non-personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, your computer’s IP address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and other statistics.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:  
•    See what data we have about you, if any.  
•    Change/correct any data we have about you.  
•    Have us delete any data we have about you.  
•    Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.  
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

### Contact Form

In order for us to contact you, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.

### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 877-736-0006 or 760-929-0039 or email us at [privacy@seoinc.com](mailto:privacy@seoinc.com?subject=privacy)
